Jagdish Mehra Collection
University of Houston Libraries
- The Book Project
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Miscellaneous (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Miscellaneous (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Acknowledgement (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Preface (with correction) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Preface (with correction) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Preface (with correction) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - The Historical Development of Quantum Theory [V.1] (Box 29)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Photocopies and Incomplete (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (photocopies) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-6 Translation (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Translation (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Index and References (with corrections) (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Proof - Galley (with corrections) (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Bound - The Historical Development of Quantum Theory (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Bound - Footnotes to Part One - The Quantum Theory of Planck, Einstein, Bohr and Sommerfeld: Its Foundation and the Rise of its Difficulties, 1900-1925 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Bound - Part One - The Quantum Theory of Plank, Einstein, Bohr and Sommerfeld: Its Foundation and the Rise of its Difficulties, 1900-1925 (Chapters three and four) (Box 34, Item 1)
  - Bound - Part One - The Quantum Theory of Planck, Einstein, Bohr and Sommerfeld: Its Foundation and the Rise of its Difficulties, 1900-1925 (Box 34, Item 2)
  - Project Outlines (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Project Outlines (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-4 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-4 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-4 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-4 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Index (with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Index (with corrections) (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (with corrections and incomplete) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (photocopies) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Miscellaneous (photocopies) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Proofs - Galley (with corrections) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Proofs - Galley (with corrections) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Proofs - Galley (with corrections) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Proofs - Galley (with corrections) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Proofs - Galley (with corrections) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Bound - The Historical Development of Quantum Theory - Part Two: The Discovery of Quantum Mechanics (Box 38, Item 1)
  - Bound - Footnotes to Part Two: The Discovery of Quantum Mechanics (Box 38, Item 2)
  - Project Outlines (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Research Material (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Research Material (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (with corrections) (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies) (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and incomplete) (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Typescript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (photocopies and with corrections) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Proofs - Galley (incomplete) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bound - The Historical Development of Quantum Theory, Part Three: The Formulation of Matrix Mechanics and its Modifications (Box 41, Item 1)
  - Bound - Footnotes to Part Three: The Formulation of Matrix Mechanics and its Modifications (Box 41, Item 2)
  - Project Outlines (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Drafts - Chapters 1-5 (incomplete) (Box 43, Folder 16)